A Guide to the Memorabilia FA437
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation Decorations, 9
  - D66: Certificate of commendation: Written in Korean and English, 1957 October 9; Mounted; 14 x 19 (Object 8001, Box 1)
  - D65c: Scroll: Written in Modern Greek with translation, 1956 September 9; Mounted; 11 X 17 (Object 8002, Box 1)
  - D59: Diploma of honor: Written in Turkish, 1955 April 29; Mounted; 13.5 X 16.5 (Object 8003, Box 1)
  - D99: Certificate: Trustees of the Rockefeller Foundation 50th Anniversary, 1963 April 30; Mounted; 11 x 16 (Object 8004, Box 1)
  - D35: Certificate of decoration: El Presidente De la Republica De Cuba; Written in Spanish, 1944 December 3; 11 x 16 (Object 8005, Box 1)
  - D44a: Certificate, parchment: The Minister of State; Written in Spanish with translation, 1945 April 14; 11.5 x 15.5 (Object 8006, Box 1)
  - D70a: Certificate of presentation of medal: O Centro De Medicina Nuclear; Written in Portugese, 1960 March 11; Mounted; 11 x14.5 (Object 8007, Box 1)
  - D67: Certificate of appreciation: The Soil Science Center of the Philippines, 1957 December 22; Mounted; 11.5 x 15.5 (Object 8008, Box 1)
  - D115: Citation: Biosciences Information Service of Biological Abstracts, 1967 October 26; 10.5 x 13.5 (Object 8009, Box 1)
  - 84: Certificate: American Hungarian Studies Foundation and Hungarian University Association, Inc, 1963 December 10; Mounted; 13 x 15 (Object 8010, Box 1)
  - 58: Textile: Embroidery from the Former Fellows in Lebanon, 1955; 18 x 19 (Object 8011, Box 1)
    Commemorative
  - D111(D2): Golden medal of honor certificate: University of Vienna; Includes translation, 1922 May; 11 x 13 (Object 8012, Box 1)
  - D80b: Certificate: Nobel Foundation; Stockholm, 1963 April 2; 10 x 13.5 (Object 8013, Box 1)
  - D54: Diploma of Honor: El Presidente De la Republica De Columbia, 1954; Mounted; 11 x 16 (Object 8014, Box 1)
  - D68b: Certificate: St. Luke Nursing University; Includes translation, 1970 October 10; Mounted; 13.5 x 18.5 (Object 8015, Box 1)
  - D101a: Certificate: St. Luke Nursing University; Includes translation, 1970 October 10; Mounted; 13.5 x 18.5 (Object 8016, Box 1)
  - 74a: Certificate: Hokkaido University; Written in Japanese; Translated testimonial and copy, 1960 September 15; 8.5 x 11 (Object 8017, Box 1)
  - 74: Catalogue description of music box: Hokkaido University; Translated testimonial and copy, 1960 September 15; 8.5 x 11 (Object 8018, Box 1)
    Memorial
  - 77: Testimonial description of album: Deep Sea Researchers by Ryofu-maru", President of Nihon Oceanographic Society testimonial and copy, 1961 November 8; 8.5 x 11 (Object 8019, Box 1)
  - D122a:: Letter of Condolence on Mr. Rockefeller's death, From Keio University, undated; 3.5 x 9 (Object 8020, Box 1)
    Correspondence
  - 88:: Copy of certificate; Testimonial and copy, 1965 June 12; 8.5 x 11 (Object 8021, Box 1)
  - 73a: Letter of thanks (translation): Letter and copy from Seishichi Ohno of Sapporo Medical College, 1960 July 8; 8.5 x 11 (Object 8022, Box 1)
  - D68a: Letter of appreciation: Korean Language Research Society, 1958 April 24; Mounted; 12 x 16 (Object 8028, Box 1)
    Certificate
  - D102: Owen Staples etching: Doorway, School of Hygiene University of Toronto, undated; Mounted; 12 x15 (Object 8029, Box 1)
    Picture
  - D30: Photograph of plaque: Image of Max Planckk Institute, 1939 February 20; 4 x 6 (postcard). Two letters attached to postcard. (Object 8030, Box 1)
    Photograph
  - D123: Certificate of election:, 1975 May 13; Letter from Douglas Dillon attached; 10 x 13 (Object 8031, Box 1)
  - D97: Letter of congratulations: Catholic University of Louvain, 1963 April 2; Enclosed in folder with ribbon and tissue paper; 12 x 16 (Object 8032, Box 1)
  - D96: Diploma of honor, undated; Mounted; 14 x 19.5 (Object 8033, Box 1)
  - D34: Certificate: La Universidad de Guadalajara, 1943 October 15; Curling on right side; 15 x 19 (Object 8034, Box 1)
  - D112: Image of certificate: Emmett I. Vaughn, 1923 May; Mounted; 9 x 11 (Object 8035, Box 1)
  - D117: Diploma of honor: Masarykova Akademie Prace, 1921 (Object 8036, Box 1)
  - D116: Letter of welcome (Cloth): Rampur Ghori Health League Partabgarh Health Unit, India, 1937 April 23; Silk freying at edges; 11.5 x 16 (Object 8037, Box 1)
    Textile
  - D32: Certificate of merit: United States Public Health Service, 1942 September 15; Mounted with seal; 11 x 13.5 (Object 8038, Box 1)
  - D62: Honorary award: Institute of Logopedics, 1956 July 11; Mounted; 10 x 12 (Object 8039, Box 1)
  - D113: Certificate of special merit: New York Employing Printers Association, Inc., 1957 January 15-17; Mounted; 12 x 15.5 (Object 8040, Box 1)
  - D114: Certificate of special merit: Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, Inc.; "For 1962 Annual Report", 1957 January 15-17; Mounted; 12.5 x 16.5 (Object 8041, Box 1)
  - D110: Diploma: Estados Unidos do Brasil; Mounted, undated; Mounted; 13.5 x 16 (Object 8042, Box 1)
  - D60: Diploma: Turk Devrim Tarihi Enstitusu; Written in Turkish, undated; Mounted; 14 x 17 (Object 8043, Box 1)
  - D78a: Certificate of participation: Film Festival of Agriculture; U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1962; Mounted; 12.5 x 16 (Object 8044, Box 1)
  - D31: Certificate: Board of Directors of The New York World's Fair 1939, 1940 January 6; Mounted; 15.5 x 18 (Object 8045, Box 1)
  - 57b: Flag: Flag of the Principality of Monaco, 1955 May 18; 38 x 50 (Object 8046, Box 2)
  - 101: Book: St. Luke Nursing University, 1970; 8 x 8.5 (Object 8047, Box 2)
  - Unknown: Award: The Lasker Group Award; Bound, 1950; 9.5 x 12 (Object 8048, Box 2)
  - 98: Certificate: The Graduate Institute of International Studies, 1963 April 2; Bound, 10 x 13.5 (Object 8049, Box 2)
  - D118: Bound certificate of appreciation: United Negro College Fund, undated; Bound, 9 x 12 (Object 8050, Box 2)
  - 40: Bound testimony: The Free University of Brussels; Written in latin; Includes letter of translation, 1946 March 12; Leatherbound in splicase, 7 x 11 (Object 8051, Box 2)
  - 86: Bound document: Includes "Statute of the Carl Zeiss Stiftung In Jena" booklet, Leatherbound in slipcase; 13 x 15 (Object 8052, Box 2)
  - 83: Model ship: Thai Library Association, undated; glass encased, 19.5 x 10 x 7 (Object 8053)
  - D20: Scroll container: Empty, 1933; 2 x 13.5 (Object 8054, Box 3)
    Contents placed in C1 and D1.
  - D124: Plaque: Inscribed "Student of Disease Theobald Smith 1859-1934", undated; 8.5 x 8.5 (Object 8055, Box 3)
  - D26:: Hommage Reconnaissant, undated; Bound with cutout pages containing ephemera, 8 x 10 (Object 8056, Box 3)
  - D29: Box: Contains stamps only, 1937 November 30; 7 x 9 x 2.5 (Object 8057, Box 17)
  - D72: Plaque: National University of Colombia, 1959 November 26; 6.5 x 8 (Object 8058, Box 3)
  - D80: Medal: Nobel Foundation, 1963 April 2; Silver, In box; 4 x 4 (Object 8059, Box 4)
  - D125: Medal, 1976 October 17; In box; 4 x 4 (Object 8060, Box 4)
  - D16: Medal, undated; In box; 3 x 4 (Object 8061, Box 4)
  - D38: Medal, undated; Bronze; Cardboard sleeve 4 x 5 (Object 8062, Box 4)
  - D6: Medal, undated; Bronze; Cardboard enclosure; Clasp on back; 4 x 4.5 (Object 8063, Box 4)
  - D100: Plaque: Instituto Nacional De Cardiologia; Written in Spanish, 1969 October; Felt box (Object 8064, Box 4)
  - T9: Seal: RF seal used by field staff in Cairo, undated (Object 8065A, Box 4)
  - T9: Stamper, undated; 3 x 9 (Object 8065B, Box 4)
  - D19b: Medal, 1927; In cardboard enclosure; 2.5 x 4 (Object 8066, Box 4)
  - D103: Medal, 1970; Bronze; In box; 3 x 3 (Object 8067, Box 4)
  - D69: Medal, 1959 October; Silver; In box; 3 x 3 (Object 8068, Box 4)
  - D37: Medal, undated; Bronze; In cardboard sleeve; 4 x4 (Object 8069, Box 4)
  - D85a: Medal: Johns Hopkins Hospital 50th Anniversary, 1964 May 14; Silver; In box; Doublesided; 4 x 4 (Object 8070, Box 4)
  - D43: Medal: Princeton University, 1947 June; Bronze; In box; (Object 8071, Box 4)
  - D56: Medal: Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith America's Legacy Award, 1955 May 11; Silver; In box; 5 x 5.5 (Object 8072, Box 4)
  - D87: Medal: Ninth International Grasslands Conference, 1965; 4 x 5 (Object 8073, Box 4)
  - D119: Medal: Educational Film Library Association-American Film Festival; Blue Ribbon Award-"Harvest", 1962; Encased in plastic (Object 8074, Box 4)
  - D120: Medal: Encased in plastic; Educational Film Library Association-American Film Festival; Blue Ribbon Award-"Rice", 1964; Encased in plastic (Object 8075, Box 4)
  - D86b: Paper document: Citation of Honor; Johns Hopkins Hospital, undated; In archival folder (Object 8076, Box 5)
  - D139: Paper document: Testimonio de Agradecimiento; Written in Spanish, 1977 August; Written in Spanish; Testimonio de Agradecimiento; In archival folder (Object 8077, Box 5)
  - D140: Paper document: Testimonio de Agradecimiento; Presented to RF; Written in Spanish, 1977 August; In archival folder (Object 8078, Box 5)
  - D142: Paper document: The Greater New York Fund Bronze Merit Award, 1966; In archival folder (Object 8079, Box 5)
  - D147: Paper document: Federal Republic of Brazil Ministry of Education and Culture, 1983 June 1; Green certificate holder; Includes typewritten note; In archival folder (Object 8080, Box 5)
  - Document holder, undated; Color illustrated; In archival folder (Object 8081, Box 5)
    Hardcover document holder
  - D146: Postage stamps, 1983 October 10; Torn along back; Framed; 13 x 15 (Object 8082, Box 6)
  - D164: Certificate, 1987 June 22; Framed; Includes paper describing item; 14 x 17.5 (Object 8083, Box 6)
  - D162: Proclamation: National Proclamation Day-Ronald Reagan; Includes letter from Frederick J. Ryan Jr., 1987 January 14; Embossed with seal; In envelope; 10 x 14.5 (Object 8084, Box 6)
  - D163: Certificate: New York Public Library Schomburg Society for the Preservation of Black Culture, In archival folder; 9 x 12 (Object 8085, Box 6)
  - D21: Scroll: Written in Arabic, 1933 December 15; Double-sided; Painted frame; 10 x 13.5 (Object 8086, Box 7)
  - D91: Scroll: Written in Spanish; Includes type-written translation on back of frame, 1968; Framed; 14 x 19 (Object 8087, Box 7)
  - D161: Plaque: International Rice Research Institute, 1986 October 15; In box (Object 8088, Box 7)
  - Unknown: Plaque: 55th Anniversary Metropolitan Insurance Company, 1979 January 1; 11 x 14 (Object 8089, Box 7)
  - D160: Medal: Semicentennial of the Pontifica Universidad Javeriana, Colombia, In blue box (Object 8090, Box 7)
  - D159: Plaque: Tufts University; Includes copy of letter from Craig L. Pritchard, 1985 August 22; 10 x 12 (Object 8091, Box 7)
  - D128: Plaque: India League of America, 1974; 10 x 14 (Object 8092, Box 8)
  - D137: Award, 1979 March 23; Framed; 12 x 17 (Object 8093, Box 8)
  - D177: Award booklet: Montblanc de la Culture; Includes newspaper clipping, 1992 April 21; 7 x 10 (Object 8094, Box 9)
  - D179: Booklet of caricatures: Al Hirschfeld drawing; 18/100; Montblanc De La Culture: The 1992 Jury of Artists (Object 8095A, Box 9)
  - D179: Booklet of caricatures: Al Hirschfeld drawing; 69/100; Montblanc De La Culture: The 1992 Jury of Artists (Object 8095B, Box 9)
  - D179: Booklet of caricatures: Al Hirschfeld drawing; Montblanc De La Culture: The 1992 Jury of Artists (Object 8095C, Box 9)
  - D180: Medal and Certificate: Includes copies of letters., 1994 April 26 (Object 8096, Box 9)
  - D181: Plaque: New Horizon Award-Crossroads Theatre Company, 1998 November 13; 10 x 13 (Object 8097, Box 9)
  - D132: Plaque: Kasetsart University, 8 x 10 (Object 8098, Box 10)
  - D127: Plaque: Universidad Nacional Agraria, 9 x 11 (Object 8099, Box 10)
  - D148: Triticale (Wheat): Mexican grown, Framed; 8 x 12 (Object 8100, Box 11)
  - D149: Plaque: International Rice Research Institute 20th Anniversary, 1980; 10 x 12 (Object 8101, Box 11)
  - D174: Plaque: International Hispanic Theatre Festival, 1990; 4 x 6 (Object 8102A, Box 11)
  - D174: Award: International Hispanic Theatre Festival, 1991; 5 x 7 (Object 8102B, Box 11)
  - D174: Award: International Hispanic Theatre Festival, 1992; 3 x 4 (Object 8102C, Box 11)
  - D176: Book, Bound book; 9 x 12 (Object 8103A, Box 12)
  - D176: Clock, 1993; In box; Photos and copy of letter separated (Object 8103b, Box 12)
  - D175: Certificate: Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene Public Health Dean's Appreciation Award; Copy of letter attached, 1992 August 23; 15 x 17 (Object 8104, Box 12)
  - D136: Plaque: Society of Builders for the Future University of Minnesota, 11 x 14 (Object 8105, Box 13)
  - D106: Plaque: American Phytopathological Society, 1972 August 10; 12 x 14 (Object 8106, Box 13)
    Testimonial
  - D170: Award: Arts & Business Council, Inc., 3 x 10 (Object 8107, Box 14)
  - D168: Plaque: Metropolitan Life Sixty-Fifth Anniversary, 1989 January 1; Brass and wood; In box; Includes letter; 3.5 x 5 (Object 8108, Box 14)
  - D171: Book: Universidad De Los Andes, Separated letter in archival folder; 10 x 13 (Object 8109A, Box 14)
  - D171: Certificate: Universidad De Los Andes, Colombia 40th Anniverary, 1988 November 16 (Object 8109B, Box 14)
  - D169: Award: Television Critics Association Outstanding Achievement, 1987 (Object 8110, Box 14)
  - D167: Artwork: Gift from Bao Ke Ming, 1989 June 6; Framed (Object 8111, Box 14)
    Miscellaneous
  - D151: Photograph: RF Agricultural Sciences Staff Seminar, 1979 November; Framed (Object 8112, Box 15)
  - D155: Award: University of Tennessee Benefactors Society, 1982; In box; 5 x 7 (Object 8113, Box 15)
  - D150: Metal plate: College of Veterinary Medicine Michigan State University Dean's Club, 6 x 12 (Object 8114, Box 15)
  - D165: Photograph: Photo of Princess Chulabhorn of Thailand; includes letter., 1988 July 31; Leather framed, 10 x 13 (Object 8115, Box 15)
  - D130: Artwork: New Perspectives Award, 1979; Framed; Leather enclosure on back with newspaper clipping; 12 x 14; (Object 8116, Box 8)
  - D156: Plaque: Tenth Thai National Corn and Sorghum Reporting Session, Metal unattached to backing; 9 x 11.5 (Object 8117, Box 16)
  - 157: Award: Institute of Food and Agricultural Sciences at the University of Florida, 1984; 11 x 12.5 (Object 8118, Box 16)
  - D152: Certificate, 1980 November; Framed; 11 x 15 (Object 8119, Box 16)
  - D158: Artwork: Watercolor painiting; Cover written in French, 12 x 16 (Object 8120, Box 16)
  - D141: Bowl: Brass, Two parts (Object 8121, Box 17)
  - D45: Certificate: Certificate and holder; University of Copenhagen, 1947 May (Object 8122, Box 18)
  - Textile, Red and gold (Object 8123, Box 18)
  - D79: Blanket, 1978 June 21; Woolen blanket (Object 8124, Box 19)
  - D131: Plaque, 1979 January; Gold tone on black base; 7.5 x 10 (Object 8125, Box 20)
  - D143: Plaque, 1981 February 10; 10 x 11 (Object 8126, Box 20)
  - D146: Plaque, 1983 October 10; Cracked along back; 6 x 8 (Object 8127, Box 20)
  - D134: Plaque, 1970 December 31; 10 x 14 (Object 8128, Box 20)
  - D129: Plaque: Bronze, 1978 June 21; In commemorative wooden box; 11 x 15 (Object 8129, Box 20)
  - D77a: Album, Hardcover; Decorative; 12 x 13 (Object 8130, Box 20)
  - D145: Medallion: Bronze, 1982 December; In box; 4 x 5 (Object 8131, Box 20)
  - D191: Book: Princeton University The First 250 Years, by Don Oberdorfer, In box sleeve; 9 x 13 (Object 8132, Box 21)
    Book
  - D192: Award: Independent Sector, In box; 8 x 10 (Object 8133, Box 21)
  - Award: Photo of H.R.H. sultan Hamengku Buwono X, In lined box; 7 x 9 (Object 8134, Box 21)
  - D184: Plate: Instiute of American Indian Arts; Plate no. 29, Red, gold, and white (Object 8135, Box 21)
  - D194: Medal: The Sir Harold Acton Medal of New York University, In box; 4.5 x 7 (Object 8136, Box 21)
  - D188: Paperweight: OPERA America award, 1988 December 9; OPERA America award (Object 8137, Box 21)
  - D187: Medallion, Silver; In box; 3 x 3 (Object 8138, Box 21)
  - D189: Medal: Cal Arts' 25th Anniversary, 1995 May 5; In box; 4 x 4 (Object 8139, Box 21)
  - D185: Medal, In box; 4 x 4 (Object 8140, Box 21)
  - D186: Medallion, 1988; In box; 3.5 x 3.5 (Object 8141, Box 21)
- Ford Foundation, 10
  - Postcard from Alvin Ailey to Susan V. Berrerford, (7.5" x 5.25") paper (Object 2012:022:001)
    POSTCARD
    Separated Materials
    Separated from: (40407) 451820448
  - Keystone Award of Excellence, 1984 October 16; (8" x 11.5") paper (Object 2012:022:002)
    AWARD
  - Ground Breaking Ceremony A Project of Harlem Interfaith Counseling Service, 1982 August 17; (11" x 14") (Object 2012:022:003)
  - Charles E. Wilson Steuben Glass Photographs, (13" x 10.5") (Object 2012:022:004)
    Separated from: (44661) 451820447
  - 3 puzzles about HIV/AIDs, 6.25" x 6.25" (Object 2012:025:003)
  - The Paul Tulane Society Postcard, (6.5" x 4.75") (Object 2012:032:001)
    Separated from: 48575/44463
  - bronze letter opener from Siam (Object 2012:033:001)
  - Welfare Planning Council Los Angela Region, presented by President., 1962 April 11; (12.5" x 10" x 0.5") Wood (Box 1)
    Separated from: (46803) 451820450
    Accession 2012:022.
  - The North Carolina Rural Economic Development Center, 1989 September 7; (10" x 8" x 1") Wood (Box 1)
  - Federation for Community Planning Human Services Institute, 2002; (13" x 9" x 1") Wood (Box 1)
  - Changing the Face of Home Ownership Neighboorhood Reinvestment Corporation, 2002 November 20; (12" x 9.5" x 0.5") Metal frame and glass (Box 1)
  - Society of Builders for the Future, (11" x 14" x 1") (Box 1)
  - The Kennedy Center African Odyssey, 1997 April-May; (7" x 6.5" x 0.25") Glass (Box 1)
  - Governor's Private Sector Initiatives Task Force Excellence Partner, (2.5" x 2.5" x .25") Metal award, separated paper 2012:022:002 (Box 1)
  - Nehru Memorial Museum and Library, 1889-1964; (6" x 6" x 0.5") Metal plate in red velvet box (7.5" x 7.5" x 1.75") (Box 1)
  - University of Florida President's Cabinet, 1991 November 15; framed (Box 2)
  - Police Executive Research Forum, 1992; (4" x 4" x 12")Glass obelisk with wooden pedestal (Box 2)
  - Egypt Ministry of Foreign Affairs, (10.5" x 10.5" x 1.5") Metal plate in blue velvet box (11.75" x 11.15" x 3.5") (Box 2)
  - Commonfund 30th Anniversary Year, 2001; (2.25" x 3.2" x 8") Glass some chips (Box 2)
  - Institute of International Education, 2000 October 16; (6" x 4" x 2") glass box with lid (Box 2)
  - The Johns Hopkins Hospital 75th Anniversary, 1964 May 14; (2.75" x 2.25" x 0.25") Metal in leather box (4.25" x 4" x 1") (Box 2)
  - International Council on Archives, (3.75" x 3.75" x 0.25") Metal in leather box (4.5" x 4.5" x 1") (Box 2)
  - A Founding Donor of the North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics, 1983 June 10; (15" x 11" x 1") Wood and Metal (Box 2)
  - ICRW International Center for Research on Women 30th Anniversary, 2006 March 8; (3" x 3" x 12") Metal sculpture with stone pedestal (Box 3)
  - The National Congress for Community Economic Development, 1994 April; (9" x 12" x 1") (Box 3)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund, 1991; (4" x 7.5" x 8") (Box 3)
  - Object from Indonesia, 2004 December; Paper note attached (8.75" x 8.5" x 7.75") Metal (Box 3)
  - Distinguished Service Award Presented by National Asian Pacific American Legal Consortium, (4" x 8" x 7") (Box 3)
  - National Urban League Million Dollar Hall of Fame, 1998 November 10; (4" x 10" x 10") (Box 3)
  - UCR Laureates, (3" x 7" x 10") glass in box (11" x 8" x 3.75") (Box 4)
  - Families and Work Institute Work Life Legacy Award, 2005; (2.25" x 7" x 9.5") (Box 4)
  - Miriam College Certificate of Appreciation, 2005 January 28; (9" x 11.5" x 0.25") (Box 4)
  - Citation Award from the Citizens of Altoona, PA, 1956 January 17; (12" x 9.5" x 0.5") bound volume with mixed formats (Box 4)
  - Birzeit University, 2005 February 5; (8.5" x 5.5" x .075") wood in box (11" x 8" x 2") (Box 4)
  - China Development Foundation for Science and Technology, metal coins in box (11" x 6" x 1.5") (Box 4)
  - Founders' Society Virginia Commonwealth University, (3" x 3" x 0.25") metal award in red velvet box (6.5" x 3.5" x 1.5") (Box 4)
  - Warren/Conner Development Coalition, 2004; (5" x 7" x 1") (Box 4)
  - Partners in Development, The Coptic Evangelical Organization, (11.5" x 9.5" x 1") wood and metal in velvet box (12.25" x 10.5" x 2.25") (Box 5)
  - Colorado State University, 2004 October 29; (8.75" x 6.75" x 3.25") wood box (Box 5)
  - Jackson State University, (10.5" x 10.5" x 1") porcelain plate (Box 5)
  - International Funders for Indigenous Peoples, 2005 April 9; (12" x 9" x 1") wood (Box 5)
  - Kent State University President's Club lapel pin, small pin (Box 5)
  - United Way, 1995-1996; (12" x 9.5" x 0.5") paper in frame (Box 5)
  - Museo de Arte de Ponce, 1995 March 16; (13" x 10.5" x 0.75") wood and plaster (Box 5)
  - The President's Medal from Laguardia Community College, 1987 September 20; (3.75" x 4.25" x 0.5") metal with velvet ribbon (Box 5)
  - LaGuardia Community College Presidential Medal Award, 1987 September 20; (12.25" x 15.25" x 0.75") paper in glass and wooden frame (Box 6)
  - Methodist Hospital of Brooklyn, 1958; (2.5" x 2.5" x 0.2") metal award (Box 6)
    Separated from: (44590) 451820445
  - Educational Film Library Association, 1979; (1" x 2.5" x 3.75") plastic (Box 6)
  - Public Education Network Founder's Award, 1998; (2.25" x 4.75" x 5.75") glass (Box 6)
  - Financial World Annual Report Award, 1957; (5" x 5" x 4.5") wood and metal (Box 6)
  - Big Brothers Big Sisters President's Circle Award, 1997; (11.5" x 1.75" x 10") plastic (Box 6)
  - The Urban Reinvestment Task Force, (1" x 8" x 10") wood and metal (Box 6)
  - 4H Club Award of the Crested Clover, 1963; (3" x 9" x 12") (Box 6)
  - Kenosha Memorial Hospital, 1974 May 16; (0.75" x 13.25" x10.75") wood and plastic (Box 6)
  - Alfred University Founders Society, 1992 February 19; (0.5" x 12" x 9.25") (Box 7)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation Service to Youth, (0.5" x 10" x 10") wood (Box 7)
  - Plans for Progress Award, 1969 May 23; (1" x 8" x 12") wood (Box 7)
  - Northside Pres. Comm. Awards, 1985 October; (1" x 8" x 8.75") wood (Box 7)
    Separated from: (44660) 451820446
  - Ministry of Civil Affairs of the People's Republic of China, 2006 January 5; (1" x 7.5" x 7.5") plastic in box (1.5" x 8" x 8") (Box 7)
  - Southern Echo, Inc., 2000 Decemb er 16; (0.75" x 13" x 10.5") (Box 7)
  - Teacher Creavity Center in Palestine, 2005; (0.75" x 7" x 9.25") wood in velvet box(2.5" x 9" x 11") (Box 7)
  - Certificate of Appreciation for support of the Kentucky Literacy Program, 1989 September 16; (12" x 9" x 0.75") wood (Box 7)
  - The Paul Tulane Society Medal, 2005 March 17; (13.75" x 11.25" x 2.25") in wooden frame (Box 8)
  - The Points of Light Foundation and the Corporation for National Service, 1997 April; (9.5" x 9" x 5") metal bowl (Box 8)
    Accession 2012:032.
  - Perpustakaan National Republik Indonesia, The National Library of Indonesia, 1996 October; (9" x 6" x 1") wooden plaque in (11" x 8.5" x 2.5") fabric box (Box 8)
  - Northside Preservation Commission Awards, (9" x 7" x 0.75") wood (Box 8)
  - Northside Preservation Commission Awards, (9" x 7" x 0.75") wood (Box 8)
  - Northside Preservation Commission Awards, 1990 September; (9" x 7" x 0.75") wood (Box 9)
  - Burmese Boy Scouts, I.F.Y. Exchange Program. Plaque presented to Ford Foundation Messrs. Fox, H. Parker, and Burness by Burma IFYE (PA #55-49), 1955 May 5; (12" x 8.5" x 1") wood, notes. (Box 9)
  - Fair Housing of the San Fernando Valley, 1977; (13" x 11" x 0.5") wood (Box 9)
  - Yale School of Management, 2012 February 24; (16.25" x 12.25" x 1") metal frame (Box 10)
  - Galilee Society, 2005 March; (13.25" x 19" x 0.25") wood and ceramic tile (Box 10)
  - Impression 5 Science Museum, 1988 March; (13" x 16" x 1") wood (Box 10)
  - ASPIRA's Organizational Growth and Development, 1996 May 16; (16.5" x 13.5" x 1") (Box 11)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League, 1966 June 18; (18" x 12" x 2") wood (Box 11)